Vasyl Suinov, Junior Front End Developer

Zaporizhzhia, Ukraine | suinov.va@gmail.com | +380689718675 | linkedin.com/in/vasyl-suinov-0b9786255

Moving to Canada in March 2023

Junior front-end developer with 9 months experience. Skilled in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Excels at creating pixel-perfect designs and working with cross-browser compatibility issues. I plan to find a job in the field of front-end development.

HIGHLIGHTS OF QUALIFICATION

HTML 5	CSS 3
SCSS	GSAP (basic level)
BEM Metodology	GIT
JuvaScript (basic level)	Swiper slider
Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Zeplin	JSON

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Zaporizhzhia, Ukraine

April 2022 - Present

Web Developer

Layout using HTML, CSS and JS based on design layouts (figma, photoshop) adaptive and cross-browser website layout, setting up functionality (buttons, sliders, forms, galleries and other elements).

https://sva-21.github.io/Funiro-porfolio/

https://sva-21.github.io/Panto-portfolio/

https://sva-21.github.io/Atova-portfolio/

https://sva-21.github.io/FarmVest-portfolio/

https://sva-21.github.io/luxtrader-portfolio/

Zaporizhzhia, Ukraine

2018 - September 2022

«UKRENERGO» company https://ua.energy/en/

Engineer in the operation of relay protection devices

Working with schemes of relay protection and emergency automation devices, with configurations of the logic of microprocessor terminals, checking operation settings, analysis of power equipment shutdowns. Oscillogram analysis, consideration of projects. Writing technical letters.

2017 – 2018	
«UKRSILENERGPROJECT	» company https://usep.com.ua/
Design engineer	
Development of power	er grid projects 0.4, 6, 10 kV. Working on a PC using Microsoft Office (word, exc
and AutoCAD softwar	e packages. Writing technical letters to clients.
Zaporizhzhia, Ukraine	
2009 – 2012	
«ZAPORIZHSTAL» plant h	ttps://zaporizhstal.com/en/
Woodworker	
Making wooden mod	lels, work on woodworking machines, work with hand tools and drawings.
	EDUCATION
Master for electrical engi	neering
Zaporizhzhia Polytechn	ic National University
2012 – 2018	
	LANGUAGES

— Russian – native.

—— English – A2. Elementary (in the process of learning).